德国  柏林
我在此传递消息一则
I am here to deliver this message.
朱海瑞将会向西方复仇
Al-Zuhari will bring down a vengeance upon the West.
这就是枪毙卡马里的刽子手
This is Kamali's executioner--
卡萨姆·纳马兹
Qassem Namazi,
朱海瑞的首席打手
Al-Zuhari's top enforcer
因其花样百出的刑讯方式而臭名昭著
and infamous for his inventive use of torture.
刑讯逼供还能有什么花样  不是吗
Well, there's nothing inventive about that, is there?
没错  但我们必须假设他们对卡马里进行了逼供
True, but we have to assume they tortured Kamali
而且他招了
and that he broke,
供出了能被朱海瑞用来反制我们的情报
giving Al-Zuhari intel he can use against us.
我不相信
I don't believe that.
今早的监控录像显示卡萨姆·纳马兹在莫斯科机场
CCTV Shows Qassem Namazi at Moscow Airport this morning,
准备搭乘飞往柏林的飞机
catching a flight to Berlin.
朱海瑞会报复所有
Al-Zuhari will be looking for retribution
与卡马里有过联系的人
against anyone connected with Kamali.
-包括他的家人  -没错
- And his family. - Yeah.
朱海瑞也会报复他的家人  这是他的行事风格
Al-Zuhari will be after them, too. It's his M.O.
他们会去找艾斯特
They're gonna go after Ester.
他来柏林就是为了她
He's here for her.
她目前正在城外的学校里
She's at school outside the city.
我们去找她
Let's go get her.
没问题  保护那个姑娘  带她回来
OK. Protect the girl and bring her in,
但这项任务才是重点
but we must stay on mission.
卡萨姆是我们找到病毒的最好机会
Qassem is our best chance of finding the virus.
这就是我们要面对的东西
This is what we're up against.
一种经过基因工程改造
It's a genetically engineered smallpox
具有惊人感染率的天花病毒
with an infection rate that is terrifying.
一旦在人群密集的区域释放...
If it's released into a populated area...
没有疫苗  也没有已知的治疗方法
We don't have a vaccine, and there is no known cure.
我们需要尽一切可能获取情报
We need all the intel we can get.
长官  他们侵入了莫斯科的"天帐"基地
Sir, they're into the Moscow crib.
肯定是卡马里告诉他们的
Kamali must have told them.
你们知道该怎么做
You know what to do.
除了安全带回艾斯特  再给我带个活口回来
Secure Ester and bring me a live one,
最好是卡萨姆
preferably Qassem.
我需要知道他们打算在何时何地使用该武器
I need to know how and when they're gonna use this weapon.
上校  这些家伙怎么办
Colonel, and these guys?
威胁解除
No longer a threat.
他来这做什么
What is he doing?
自有他的道理
What's necessary.
我们知道你是实验室成员  瓦丽妮博士
We know your involvement at the lab, Dr. Valigny,
也知道你们都注射了疫苗
and we know you're all vaccinated,
我们需要疫苗
and we need that vaccine.
从我的血液中分离抗体需要几个月的时间
It will take you months to extract it from my blood.
而任何被病原感染的人
Anyone infected with the strain they're using
几天内就会丧命
will be dead within days.
我要去大使馆
I want to see my embassy!
没问题
Ok.
但有件事你必须明白
But there is something you need to understand.
你已经死在了德列兹纳实验室
You died at the Drezna facility.
所以你也只能装在裹尸袋里
So the only way you'll make it back to your embassy
运回你的大使馆
is in one of these.
除非你能告诉我一些有用的情报
Unless you can give me something I can use.
竹中此前有跟一位德国人打交道
Takenaka dealt with a German,
是个商人
a businessman.
莫罗·萨利
Maroun Saleh.
所有供给都要经他之手
All the supplies went through him.
所有研究都是莫罗·萨利资助的
Maroun Saleh funded the whole operation.
莫罗·萨利  走吧
Maroun Saleh. Let's go.
请放我走
Please let me go.
不  不
No, no! No!
阿迈  你这几天感觉怎么样
How you feeling these days, Mikey?
都康复了吗
You all better?
不  还没有完全恢复
No, not 100%,
但哥罩你还是没问题的  不是吗
but, uh, I still got your back, yeah?
这是必须的  兄弟
Yeah. I never doubted that, bud.
不得不说  当我从实验室救你出来的时候
Got to say, though, when I picked you up from that lab,
我以为你再也爬不起来了
thought you were down for the count.
是啊  我也这么想的
Yeah. So did I.
你有没有觉得凡是我们接手的事都会变的倒霉透顶
You ever feel like everything that we touch just turns to shit?
这整件事都糟糕透了  迈克
This whole thing's a mess, Mike.
那孩子的父亲因为我们而死
That kid's dad's dead because of us.
或许我们本应该沿着那条路一直骑到墨西哥的
Maybe we should have stayed on that road to Mexico.
是啊  或许吧
Yeah, maybe.
好事做到底
Let's see this through,
我们要坚守对卡马里的承诺  确保艾斯特的安全
keep our promise to Kamali, make sure Ester's safe.
没错
Yeah.
发现萨利
Eyes on Saleh.
目标正在移动
Target on the move.
他跟同伙在一起
He's got company.
能抓住他吗
Can you grab him?
除非混战一场
Not without leaving a mess.
好吧  跟住他  有机会就活捉
OK. Stay with him. Take him if you can.
收到
Copy that.
该死
Bloody hell.
我操  这是学校?
Holy fuck! That's a school?
没错  你对这环境不陌生吧?
Yeah. So you're familiar with the concept, huh?
学校?  当然
School? Yeah.
我在那学会了抽烟  喝酒  打架
It's where I learned hot smoke, drink, and fight.
好了  我们去带艾斯特出来
All right. Let's get Ester out.
然后去抓卡萨姆
Then we'll go get Qassem, huh?
好  我在车里等你
Yeah. I'll be here.
请问  你认识艾斯特·卡马里吗
Excuse me. Do you know Ester Kamali?
最好去问她们
Better ask them.
-那群姑娘?  -嗯
- Those girls? - Mm-hmm.
谢谢
Thanks.
姑娘们  打扰了
Hey, girls. Sorry to interrupt.
知道艾斯特在哪吗
Do you know where Ester is?
关你什么事
What's it to you?
我是她家里的朋友
I'm a family friend.
有钱吗
Got any money?
还玩敲诈  好极了
Extortion, huh? That's great.
她在哪
Where is she?
她舅舅给了我们50块呢
Her uncle gave us 50.
她舅舅?
Her uncle?
你去左边
Go to the left over there.
你去前面
Go straight, yeah?
好了  我们到那去
OK. Let's go over there.
找到那个姑娘  活捉卡萨姆  车里见
Find the girl, bring in Qassem, and I'll meet you at the car.
收到
Copy that.
这些气球真好看
These balloons are cute.
阿迈  看到艾斯特了
Mikey, eyes on Ester.
-快滚  小子  -达米恩?
- Beat it kid. - Damien?
-不好意思  -达米恩  你来这做什么
- Sorry. - Damien, what are you doing here?
你得跟我走
You got to come with me.
不  你来这做什么
No. What are you doing here?
艾斯特  该走了
Ester, we got to go.
有人在找你  他们可不是好人
There's some guys looking for you, and they're not very nice.
快走  快跟我走
Come on. Just come on.
我好得很  放手
I'm fine. Get off me.
艾斯特
Ester!
-艾斯特  等等  -卡萨姆
- Wait, Ester. - Hey, Qassem.
你怎么会在这儿
What are you doing here?
阿迈  过来
Mikey, on me.
卡萨姆在这
Qassem is here.
你能靠近他吗
Can you get to him?
一言难尽
It's complicated.
我在章鱼船旁边
I'm by that ride with the octopus.
终于找到你了  大家都很担心
I found you. We were worried.
你朋友是谁
Who's your friend?
没事的  他认识我爸爸
He's fine. He knows my dad.
你爸爸在等你
Your dad is waiting.
-站住  -我带你去见他
- Stop. - Let me take you to him.
我们走
Let's go.
不许动
Don't move!
他是我爸爸的朋友  不会有事的
He's a friend of my dad's. It's fine, honestly.
艾斯特  问他为什么带了那么多杀手
Ester, ask him why he's here with a bunch of killers.
为了保护你
To protect you.
我是看着艾斯特长大的
I've known Ester all her life.
你是她什么人
What's she to you,
一枚任你摆布的棋子吗
an asset, someone to use?
闭嘴
Shut up.
艾斯特  那人不是你爸的朋友
Ester, that man is no friend of your dad's.
我爸在哪呢
Yeah. Where is my dad?
走吧  我们走
Come on, come on. Let's go. Come on.
你他妈的别动
Hey! Don't fucking move.
达米恩  你在干什么
Damien, what are you doing?
艾斯特  放心  没事的
Ester, it's all right, it's OK.
你打算做什么
What are you gonna do, huh?
在大庭广众之下向我开枪吗
You gonna shoot me here in front of everybody, huh,
当着她的面?
in front of her?
-我可没有武器  -放屁
- I am unarmed. - Bullshit.
你以为我会信你吗
You think I'd believe any word you'd say?
-走吧  艾斯特  -别碰她
- Come on, Ester. - Don't touch her.
艾斯特  过来
Ester, come here.
-你爸在等你  -别过去  跟我走
- Your dad is waiting for you. - Don't go to him. Walk to me.
你爸在等着呢  我带你去  快点
Your dad is waiting. Let me take you to him. Come on.
-他撒谎  -快来
- He's not. - Come on.
-艾斯特  他撒谎  -你爸在等你
- Ester, he's not. - Your dad is waiting for you.
艾斯特
Ester.
他撒谎
He's not.
怎么  你不想见你爸爸吗
What, you don't want to see your dad?
-别听他的  -我想见我爸
- Don't listen to him. - I want to see my dad.
那就走啊  快
OK. Let's go. Come on.
-艾斯特  你不能去见他  -快走啊
- Ester, you can't see him. - Let's go.
你爸在等你呢
Your dad is waiting for you.
-艾斯特  -为什么  他只是想...
- Ester. - But why? He just wants me to--
-快走  -为什么我不能见他
- Come on. - Why can't I go see him?
快走啊
Come on!
因为他已经死了
Because he's dead, all right?
他杀了你爸  我亲眼目睹
He shot him! I saw him do it.
撒谎  他在骗你
That's a lie. He's lying to you.
-艾斯特  -艾斯特
- Ester. - Ester.
闭嘴
Shut up!
我们现在就去见他  艾斯特  跟我走
Let's go to him now. Come on, Ester.
你想见你爸吗
You want to see your dad?
-我们现在就去找他  -闭嘴
- Let's go and see him now. - Shut up!
不
No!
闪开  闪开
Move, move!
趴下  趴下  快走
Down, down! Go!
阿迈你在哪  艾斯特跑了
Where are you, Mikey? Ester's run off.
离你不远
Seconds away.
开枪啊
Come on.
操
Fuck!
艾斯特
Ester!
阿迈  我找到她了
I got her, Mikey.
你抓一个活的我们就离开  怎么样
Grab a live one, let's get out of here, huh?
收到  在车上等你
Roger that. I'll be in the car.
他真的死了吗
Is he really dead?
-抱歉  艾斯特  -不
- I'm sorry, Ester. - No.
过来
Come here.
快走  快走
Move, move, move!
蹲下  待在那儿
Get down! Stay there.
小心别伤到那个女孩
Careful with the girl.
操
Fuck.
掩护我
Cover me.
该死
Fuck.
快上  上
Move! Move!
上
Go.
拿着这把钥匙
I need to take this key.
该死
Fuck!
那边那辆黑色奔驰
The black Mercedes over there.
是我们的车
It's our car.
上车  然后趴下
I want you to get in it, I want to get on the floor,
待在那别动
and I want you to stay there.
那你怎么办
What are you gonna do?
-不用担心我  知道吗  -好
- Don't you worry about me, all right? - OK.
数到三  做好准备
On 3. Get ready to move.
-准备好了吗  -嗯
- Ready? - Yep.
一
1...
我们在游乐场后面
We're at the back.
二
2...
兄弟  你他妈最好知道些有用的情报
Ooh, you. You better have some fucking good intel on you, mate.
三  走
3. Go!
该死
Fuck!
拦住她
Cut her off!
操
Fuck!
这机灵的鬼东西
Sneaky little shit.
达米恩  快来
Come on, Damien! Hurry!
车子比我开得还好
She drives better than me.
走开
Move!
快点  兄弟
Hurry up, bud.
你想要我放弃这个情报吗
You want me to drop this intel?
他可重了[可有价值了]
He's quite heavy.
然后惹洛克发火?  当然不行
And piss Locke off? No, no, no.
用你的肌肉啊
Use your muscles.
至少我还有肌肉  就来了
At least I have some. I'm coming to you.
艾斯特  到后座去  快
Ester, get in the back! Get in the back!
快点快点  斯科特
Come on, come on, Scott.
操  阿迈  我朝你过去了
Fuck! Coming to you, Mikey.
快点
Come on.
打开后备箱  打开后备箱
Open the boot, open the boot!
迈克  你的情报还活着吗
Is that intel alive, Mike?
亲爱的醒醒  醒醒
Wake up, babe. Wake up.
该死
Shit!
他本来是活着的  开车开车
He was alive! Move, move, move!
总部  我们已瞄准萨利
Zero, we've targeted Saleh.
现在发送图像和坐标
Sending you visuals and coordinates.
这是李扎·哈桑  朱海瑞的左臂右膀
That's Reza Hassan, Al-Zuhari's right-hand man.
自德列兹纳之后我们就失去了他的行踪
We lost track of him after Drezna.
一网打尽
Full house.
你还好吗
You all right?
给你拿了这个
Brought you that.
不用了  谢谢
No, thanks.
你没事吧  孩子
How you doing, kid?
你觉得呢
How do you think I'm doing?
我知道你很难过
I know you're hurting.
你怎么知道我是什么感受
How do you know what it feels like?
孩子  我是军人
I'm a soldier, kid.
我知道痛苦的滋味
I know pain.
但他是我爸爸
Yeah, but he was my dad.
艾斯特  我从没和别人提起过...
I haven't told anyone this before, Ester, but...
其实我也是个父亲
I'm a dad, too.
如果出事的是你  他们会作何感受
How would they feel if it was you?
老实说
Honestly...
不知道
don't know.
他们一定很爱你
Well, they must love you.
他们不认识我
They don't know me.
抱歉
Sorry.
不是你的错  孩子
It's not your fault, kid.
但你还是个父亲  不是吗
You're still a dad, though, right?
这才是最重要的
That's all that matters.
但我做的远远不够吧
Yeah. Not much of one, huh?
我爸爸几乎不在我身边
Mine was hardly ever around.
他似乎一直很忙碌
There always seemed to be something else.
总是不在家
You know, he was away a lot, and...
总是有理由
there was always an excuse,
但每当他离开时
but whenever he was away,
我内心总觉得他会回来
there was a little part of me that always knew he'd come back.
是啊
Yeah.
过来
Come here.
他再也回不来了
He's not coming back.
他死了
He's gone.
-嘿  -你怎么样
- Hey. - How you doing?
要出发了
We're up.
她怎么样
How is she?
-她是个坚强的孩子  -没错
- Eh, she's a tough little kid, you know? - Yeah.
你呢
And you?
我没事
I'm all right.
只是得理顺我这操蛋的人生
Just got to sort out my fucking life.
我给你点时间
I'll give you a second.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了
Ok.
莫罗·萨利
All right. Maroun Saleh.
瓦丽妮透露他资助了德列兹纳实验室
According to Valigny, he helped fund the Drezna facility.
我们跟踪他去了一个朱海瑞的训练营
We track him down to an Al-Zuhari training camp,
他在那和老朋友李扎·哈桑见了面
where he met our old friend Reza Hassan.
如果能活捉他们  是活捉
If we can extract these two alive--alive--
那我们既抓获了朱海瑞的左右手还能得到病毒的线索
we have Al-Zhuari's number two and a track line to the virus.
详细转告斯科特  行吗
Make sure Scott's fully briefed, will you?
明白
Roger that.
情报在迈克那
Mike has the intel.
你知道死人和活人的区别吗
Do you know the difference between a dead man and a live man?
当然  死人不用交税
Yeah. Dead men don't pay taxes.
知道这个就够了
Consider yourself briefed.
总部  B1  B2已就位
Zero, Bravo One and Two in position.
已完成撤退准备
Ready to extract on your command.
喂  奇奇
Hey, Bridgey.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- You good? - Good.
行动
Go.
前进
Moving.
闭嘴
Shut up!
妈的
Oh, shit!
前进
Moving!
哈桑  救我出去
Hassan, Hassan, get me out! Hassan!
总部  发现萨利
Zero, we got eyes on Saleh.
捉住他  阿迈
Get him, Mikey, get him!
离远点  手举起来
Get away! Hands!
你不该向他开枪  阿迈
Not supposed to shoot him, Mikey.
打在腿上  死不了
It's his leg. He'll live!
举手  举手
Hands. Hands!
不准动  不然开枪了
Don't fucking move, or I'll shoot you.
我是B1  我们抓住了哈桑和萨利
Bravo One. We have Hassan and Saleh.
还发现了一个保险箱
We also have a safe.
我们需要保险箱里的东西
We need what's in there,
至少带一个活的回来
and bring me one of them alive.
明白
Roger that.
打开保险箱
Open the safe. Open the safe.
你  起来  起来
You, get up! Get up!
打开保险箱
Open that safe.
立刻打开保险箱
Open the fucking safe right now!
-我照做  照做  -快点
- I'll do it, I'll do it. - Right now!
我照做
I'll do it.
过来
Come here!
他妈的
Jesus Christ!
迈克  他会失血而亡的
Mike, he's gonna bleed out.
没错
Yeah.
快打开这该死的保险箱
Open the fucking safe right now!
开枪啊
Go ahead.
我不怕死
I'm not afraid to die.
快点  开枪啊
Come on. Do it, do it!
该死的信徒
Fucking beleivers.
开枪啊
Do it.
他不会就范了  炸开吧
He's not gonna do it. Just blow it.
交给我了
Got him.
老实跪好
Get on your fucking knees!
妈的
Fuck!
-快点  -待着别动
- Come on! - Stay there.
妈的  迈克  快点
Fuck, Mike. Come on.
快点  哥们
Come on, bud.
二十秒  再给我二十秒
20 more seconds. I need 20 more seconds.
快点  他们要从门那边过来了
Come on. They're coming through the door, Mike.
你老实待在那
You stay there.
你他妈在做高数题吗  快炸
What are you doing, fucking math? Blow it.
这是个技术活  需要时间的好吗
It's like a Soufflé. It takes time.
妈的  斯科特
Ugh! Shit, Scott.
快点  阿迈
Come on, Mikey.
待着别动
Stay there!
-安装完毕  -好了吗
- Good! - We're good?
小心爆炸
Fire in the hole!
竟然炸开了  迈克尔
That fucking worked, Michael!
-是炸开了  -干得漂亮
- Yeah, that worked. - Did a great job on that one.
-妈的  好烫  -操
- Shit, that's hot! - Fuck!
我觉得我找到了重要文件
I think I've got the important bits.
但愿如此
You better hope so.
-掩护我  -好
- Cover me. - Yeah.
-找到了什么  -一些硬盘
- What you got? - I got some hard drives.
快离开这
Let's get the fuck out of here.
明白
Got you.
总部  我是B1  准备撤退
Zero, Bravo One. We're heading for exfil.
-立刻撤退  -站起来
- Exfil immediate. - Stand up!
向你靠近  斯科特
Coming to you, Scott.
这就是我们不打人腿的原因
This is why we don't shoot people in the leg.
都没法好好走路了  哥们
Makes it hard for them to walk, bud.
是啊  唧唧歪歪
Yeah. Nag, nag, nag.
妈的
Fuck!
你看到什么了
What do you got?
外面有四到五个人
Got 4 or 5 of these guys.
还看到了卡萨姆
I got eyes on Qassem, too.
总部  我们抓到了哈桑并取得了情报
Zero, we have Hassan and the intel.
还有三十秒
30 seconds.
让你的人退后
Tell your men to stand down.
他们会先杀了我
They'll kill me first.
走着瞧  走  快走
Let's see. Walk, walk.
退后  否则崩了他  我发誓
Back off! I'll put a bullet in him, I swear to God!
看见没
See?
好的  好的
Ok, ok.
你是个大人物
You're a popular guy.
他们不会向你开枪的
They're not gonna shoot you.
他们爱死你了
They love you.
杀了我
后退  后退
Back, back, back, back!
-他妈的  -妈的
- Fucking hell! - Holy shit!
总部  我们需要撤退支援
Zero, we need a hot extraction now!
还有三十秒
30 seconds.
去你妈的
Fuck off!
撑不了三十秒了
We don't have 30 seconds!
你没事吧
You all right?
把外面的人统统干掉  阿迈
Fucking kill all the guys out there, Mikey.
该死
Shit!
那是我们的直升机  伙计
That's our fucking ride, mate.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
好吧
All right.
放绳子
Drop the line.
我看见绳子了  绳子放下来了
I see the rope. The rope's down.
冲了
Going.
前进
Moving!
两点方向  瑞姆
On your two, Richmond.
快点  上
Come on! Go!
抓紧绳子
Take the rope now!
上  上  上
Go, go, go, go!
-你没事吧  -没事
- You good? - Yeah.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
哦  该死
Oh, shit!
你好啊  老大
Hi, boss.
妈的
Shit!
很高兴见到你们
We're glad to see you guys.
你带了什么东西
What you got for me?
我们拿到原始数据了  宝贝儿
We got the mother lode, baby!
是的
Yeah.
有了
All right.
你会爱死我们的
Oh, you're gonna love us.
怎么烧焦了
Why is it burnt?
得问这位搞爆破的
Ask demolition man here.
给  计算机的玩意儿
There. Computer stuff.
你们是去找萨利的
You went in for Saleh.
他人呢
Where is he?
他被哈桑干掉了
He was killed by Hassan.
那么哈桑呢
And where's Hassan?
被卡萨姆干掉了
He was killed by Qassem.
他们就这么自相残杀?
So, what, they all just killed each other?
没错  差不多就这么回事
Yeah, pretty much.
要都这样  还要我们出马干嘛
Makes you wonder why we even needed to be there, huh?
下次  死要见尸
Next time, just bring me a body,
最好是还没死透的
preferably warm.
明白  长官
Yes, boss.
干的漂亮
Good work.
是啊
Yeah.
我知道他干了什么
I know what he's done.
上校
Colonel...
安德森给北约上传了假的身份信息
Andersson uploaded false identities to the NATO system.
这是我找到的第一个
This is the first one that I found.
他有过去几个月完整的北约工作纪录
He has a complete NATO history going back several months,
一个特务
a clean skin.
还有多少?
How many more are there?
我不清楚
I don't know.
我已经找出了安德森使用的电子标记
I've worked out the tag Andersson used to mark them,
但数据被烧毁的太厉害
but the data's too fire-damaged.
这家伙用的是什么身份
So what's this guy's cover?
根据系统记录  他叫马丁·诺文尼
The system has him down as Martin Novotny,
上士
Sergeant First Class,
是捷克代表团的联络员
staff liaison officer for the Czech delegation.
他会出席明天举行的
He's due to attend the meeting tomorrow
北约军事委员会议
for the NATO military committee.
这支代表团会驻扎在哪
Where's the delegation being held?
法兰克福市
Frankfurt.
诺文尼现在在哪
Where's Novotny now?
捷克代表团昨晚上了一辆火车
Czech delegation boarded an overnight train yesterday.
抵达法兰克福市中心预计还要...
ETA Frankfurt Central...
该死  两小时二十分钟
Fuck! 2 hours, 20 minutes.
北约会议是散播病毒的绝佳地点
That NATO meeting's the perfect target for the virus.
让飞行员去截拦那辆火车
Give the pilot an intercept course.
然后联系北约指挥中心
Then contact NATO Command.
我需要一支生化应急小组待命
I want a full HAZMAT team on standby.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
好了  都听着
Right. Listen up.
诺文尼是我们的目标
Novotny is our target.
你们几个  准备爬火车
You lot, you're gonna catch a train.
这才七点  现在喝酒是不是早了点
什么叫开始  我们就没停过
干杯  诺文尼上士
你们要找到诺文尼  并阻止他
You find Novotny and you stop him.
找一份捷克代表团的名单
Pull up a list of the Czech delegates.
告诉我他们中间
Find proof that at least
至少有一个人的身份是真实的
one of them is who they really claim to be.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
手  手拿出来  手都拿出来
Hands. Show me your hands, show me your hands.
-坐下  手举起来  -怎么回事
- Sit up, hands up. - What is this?
看着我  看着我
Look at me, look at me.
-别干蠢事  -手举起来  手举起来
- Don't fucking do that. - Hands up, hands up.
-看着我  -交给我了  别担心
- Look at me. - I got him. Don't worry.
别逞英雄
Don't be a hero.
看着我
Look at me.
喂
Oi!
你们是什么人
Who the hell are you people?
检票员
Ticket inspectors.
他不在这
He's not here.
这是怎么回事儿
What is this?
她会解释的
She'll explain.
没错  你们继续
Yeah, right. You go ahead.
我来处理外交问题
I'll just deal with the diplomacy.
说"外交"也太浮夸了
Diplomacy's overrated anyway.
没事  我们是北约部队
It's OK. We're NATO forces.
来这儿找个人
Just here looking for somebody.
妈的让开  坐下
Get the fuck out of the way! Get down!
上尉  我得走了
Captain, I got to go.
她没事吧
Is she OK?
我中弹了
I'm hit,
诺文尼在火车上有同伙
and Novotny was not alone on the train.
我干掉了一个  但可能还有其他人
I took one out, but there may be others.
坚持住B3  我们会尽快你弄出来
Bravo 3, hang tight. We'll get you out.
找到了  安东·派勒契克少将
I've got it. Major General Anton Palecek.
帮我接通他的电话
Get me through to him.
我们已发现目标
We've got eyes on target.
操  操他妈的
Fuck! Motherfucker.
总部  他在车厢里释放病毒了
Zero, he's released the virus in the carriage.
车厢里大约有20至30个平民
We got about 20 or 30 civilians in there.
车上还有他的同伙
He's got some friends with him, too.
你他妈在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
畜生  操
Motherfucker! Fuck!
喂  站住
Oi! Stop!
那节车厢被感染了  明白吗
That carriage is infected, all right?
我女朋友在里面
My girlfriend is in there.
我必须得进去
I have to go inside.
-别  别  -待在这别动
- No, no, no, no! - Stay here.
你要敢进去  敢碰那扇门的话
You go in there, you touch that door,
我就打死你  明白吗
I shoot you, am I clear?
明白
Yes.
抱歉  小伙子
Sorry, kid.
我们从这上去
Let's go up and over.
-我要出去  -别慌  别慌
- I want to get out! - Don't panic, don't panic.
听我说
Listen to me.
他们告诉我里面有病毒
They told me there is a virus inside.
什么
What?!
漂亮啊  蜘蛛侠
Nice work, Spider-Man.
去你妈的蜘蛛侠  哥们
Screw, Spider-Man, dude.
那家伙穿的可是紧身衣
Guy wears tights.
长官  接通派勒契克了
Sir, Palecek.
派勒契克将军  我是菲利浦·洛克上校
Genera Palecek, this is Lieutenant Colonel Philip Locke,
英国特种部队
British Special Forces.
我想你已获悉  我们现在有紧急情况
As I'm sure you're aware, we have an emergency.
一种4级传染病毒已经扩散
A level 4 contagion has been released.
不要让任何人离开那节车厢
Do not let anyone out of that carriage.
重复  不要让任何人离开那节车厢
I repeat. Do not let anyone out of that carriage.
是
Sir.
门卡住了
It's stuck.
听我说  听着
Listen to me, listen.
任何人不得离开这节车厢
No one is to leave this carriage,
谁敢离开  我就打死谁
and I will shoot the first person who tries.
你们必须解开被感染车厢的挂钩
You have to unhook the infected carriage.
5分钟后火车就会进入居民区
5 minutes before it reaches a populated area.
明白了吗
Do you copy?
总部  明白  我们去把车钩炸掉
Zero, we copy. We're gonna blow the coupling.
我们不能让车厢进入城市
We can't let it reach the city.
明白
Roger that.
要我来炸吗
You want me to do it?
就你炸保险箱那鸟样
After the safe?
还是我来吧
I got this one, I think.
好吧  人家那是第一次嘛
All right. Well, there's a first time for everything.
C4炸弹在这儿
C4's in here.
快点  我去前面找诺文尼
Let's go. I'm gonna push forward and find Novotny.
别把自己炸飞了
Don't blow yourself up.
操
Fuck!
迈克
Mike!
我没事
I'm all right!
斯科特  手雷
Scott, grenade!
B2  B2
Bravo Two, Bravo Two!
他没有炸掉车钩
He didn't blow the carriages.
B1  我们失去了B2
Bravo One, we've lost Bravo Two.
他妈的
Shit!
你得继续完成任务
You've got to stay on mission.
你必须让火车停下  迈克尔
You have to stop that train, Michael.
明白
Roger that.
操
Fuck.
你没事吧
Alles OK?
我没事  孩子
Yeah. I'm all good, kid.
这机车不错
That's a nice bike.
又见面了  好兄弟
Hey, buddy boy!
你刚才不是死了吗
Didn't you just die?
快去让火车停下
Go stop the train!
我要去追诺文尼
I'm going after Novotny!
总部
Zero...
诺文尼杀了司机  并毁了刹车
Novotny's killed the driver and disabled the brake.
火车一分钟后进入市郊
One minute until you hit the suburbs.
B2  不惜一切代价
Bravo Two, whatever it takes,
让火车停下
stop the train.
给我出来
Get out of the fucking truck!
给我从车里出来
出来  就现在
Out! Now.
滚开
Fuck off!
妈的
Fuck.
操  别捣乱
Fuck! Honestly.
蠢狗  知道厉害了吧
Fucking pussy of a dog.
迈克
Mike?
要怎么才能弄死你
What's it take to kill you, huh?
地理坐标已锁定
Grid reference coordinates locked in.
生化应急小组在路上了
HAZMAT team on their way.
明白
Roger.
那里有个活的
We've got a live one there!
他已经不喘气了  迈克
He's not very alive, Mikey.
真倒霉
Oh, shit.
老大又要不高兴了
Boss ain't gonna like that.
这里是B1和B2
Bravo One and Bravo Two here.
我们让火车停下了
Uh, we stopped the train.
诺文尼死了  重复  我们的情报没了
Novotny's dead. I repeat. Our intel is dead.
出了什么事
What's going on?
他们会来帮助你们的  明白吗
They are coming to help you, OK?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这就是你想到让火车停下的方法?
So that was your idea of how to stop a train, was it?
它停下了  不是吗
We stopped it, didn't we?
干的好  斯科特
Good job, Scott.
这些人能活下去吗
These people got any chance?
除非我们能找到治疗办法
Only if we can find a cure.
看来是活不成了
So no.
你让我担心了一下下
You had me worried for a second.
真的吗
Yeah? Heh.
你是想顺便蹭一天假吗
Now is this what you have to do to get a day off?
你们刚才的表演可牛了
That was some stunt you guys pulled back there.
多谢夸奖
Yeah. Thanks.
你自己多保重
You take care of yourself, yeah?
你也是
Yeah. You, too.
如果不想和我拥抱
If I'm not gonna get a hug,
起码来个英国式握手嘛
give me one of those famous Limey handshakes.
回见
See you soon.
以伟大而慈悲的真主之名
In the name of Allah the great and merciful,
汝等必须洗清自己的罪孽
you must cleanse yourselves of your sins,
真主已经允诺
as he has promised us that paradise awaits
那些为我们的自由和信仰而战的人
those of you who lay down your lives in this war,
你们牺牲后的灵魂将升入天堂
fighting for our freedom and what we believe.
长官  来自皮拉戈娃的消息
Sir, a message from Pirogova.
乌尔诺夫离开了他在莫斯科的别墅
Ulyanov has left his Dacha in Moscow.
他开始行动了
He's on the move.
他正在来德国的路上
He's heading for Germany.
他是来找那两个小子的对吧
He's coming for the boys, isn't he?
让皮拉戈娃盯住他
Tell Pirogova to stay with him.
是
Sir.
柏林  20号分部安全屋
你看见他的块头了吗
Did you see the size of him?
简直跟他妈野人一样
He was a fucking sasquatch.
可他是把你扔下火车的
Now he threw you off the train.
滚蛋  下次大块头交给你
Fuck you! Next time, you fight the big guy.
浑身酸痛吗  报应
Sore, huh? Good.
你给艾斯特买了什么
So what did you buy Ester?
不知道  伙计
I don't know, dude.
几本垃圾德国杂志
Some shitty German mags.
不过我还买了这个
I did get her these.
她会喜欢的伙计  这眼镜真不错
She's gonna love those, mate. They're brilliant.
真的?
You think?
我不知道
I have no idea.
不知道小女孩喜欢什么
I don't know what teenage girls like.
我也不知道  可怜的孩子
Neither do I. Poor kid.
她只剩我们可以依靠了
We're all she's got.
斯科特
Scott...
门
the door.
上
Go.
总部  有人侵入了安全屋
Zero, safe house has been breached.
我上楼
Going up.
明白
Yeah.
艾斯特
Ester?
手举起来
Hands! Hands!
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
艾斯特  艾斯特
Ester? Ester?
达米恩
Damien?
来我这儿  没事了
Come here. Come on.
你没事吧
You all right?
没事
Yeah.
斯科特  斯科特
Scott! Scott!
不  不  别
No. No, no, no. Don't.
卡萨姆  放下枪
Qassem, put that gun down.
-放下枪  -别  达米恩
- Put that gun down. - No, Damien.
放下你该死的枪
Put that fucking gun down!
不  达米恩  别再杀人了
Please, Damien. No more killing!
他绝不会杀她
He was never going to kill her.
你胡说八道什么  迈克
What are you talking about, Mikey?
爸爸
Dad?